Isaac Westcott...
What on earth are you?
What is you desire?
What do you even keep doing this for?
I was only ten when I first became
aware of what kind of person I was.
It was my mother's death.
I lamented the death of my kind mother.
However,
I felt more elation than sadness.
The grief and despair filling that place
brought me joy and excitement.
Apparently my sensibilities are rather
different from a normal person's.
Though I've lived my life careful
not to let others learn about that.
Not even my closest friends.
I told you, straining that hard
won't do any good.
Calm your emotions, and do it
like you're gently touching them.
I'll show you one more time, so watch.
Go on, once more.
Yeah!
Look, I just said...
Elliot, Ellen.
So this is where you've been?
Ike.
Yeah.
As you can see, we're practicing magic.
Ellen is still struggling
to get the knack for it, after all.
But I just can't do it that well!
Elliot, you and Ike are both able to
use magic even better than the adults.
It's not fair.
Karen can do it, right?
I wonder how there can be
such a difference between sisters?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
That was bad of me.
Ahh, don't cry.
It's all right, Ellen.
I'll help you too,
so let's all head to the training grounds.
If we practice outside we'll get yelled at
by the teachers again.
The adults are all scaredy-cats.
No outsiders would ever choose
to come to such a remote place like this.
They have no choice.
Magi like us have always been
persecuted for ages.
Especially during our parents'
and teachers' generation.
Back then we were always together.
Ellen, Elliot, me,
and Ellen's little sister, Karen.
Even so, I think they're being too fearful.
The teachers would never lose
a fight against a normal person.
Not as long as they came in small numbers.
But it would be a different story
if it was one against a hundred,
or one against a thousand, right?
Well, yeah...
People fear that which is different from them.
And that fear gives rise
to violence and madness.
Keeping our true nature hidden
is the most virtuous thing we can do.
I don't really understand
what you're talking about.
Our village...
Sister, why?
Why is this happening?
Elliot!
You can't go.
But!
What we have to do right now
is protect Ellen and Karen.
At some point I began to long for
even greater elation than
my mother's death brought.
And in that moment
I also felt joy close to that.
Along with a survivor's sadness
and despair over those who died.
Elliot, Ellen, Karen.
Let's create a world for magi.
Let's banish humanity and create
a world exclusively for us magi.
They were the ones who started this.
So there's no reason we shouldn't do it, right?
I won't forgive them...
Not ever!
Thank you for granting me
this opportunity to exact vengeance.
I'll avenge them.
Thank you for granting me
this opportunity to exact vengeance.
From today onward,
we're the only allies we have.
The entire world is our enemy!
That's right!
Let's recreate this world!
Thank you
for making me
the victim.
Afterwards, the four of us took shelter
temporarily in the city's orphanage.
Of course we kept our origins hidden.
Roughly three years later,
I was adopted by a wealthy couple.
Eventually they met
"an unfortunate accident" and died,
leaving their wealth to me.
I called Elliot, Ellen, and Karen to my side,
and we dedicated ourselves
to researching magic.
All to uncover a way to exact vengeance
on this world and everyone in it.
Then the day finally came.
Karen, get ready.
Yes.
Ike, this Spirit Formula...
Yes, it will create a Spirit.
It'll gather all the mana in the world into
a single point and create a brand new lifeform.
Along with a brand new world
that covers this one.
A Territory.
An omnipotent space where someone
can make whatever they imagine a reality.
If my calculations are correct,
the space possessed
by the Spirit born from this
should be large enough to cover all of Earth.
It'll be large enough
to call a Neighboring World,
a world that borders our own.
That will be our world.
We'll overwrite this world
with the Neighboring World.
I predict there will be
a shock wave when the Spirit manifests.
Elliot, prepare the protective wards.
Yeah.
You seem slightly different than before.
Perhaps you've recalled the fact
that I killed you
when you were Shinji Takamiya?
Why you!
Seems I hit the mark.
I had anticipated that once
Deus revealed herself,
but once again I'm reminded
that power is truly wonderful.
Though this puts me in a troublesome spot.
I'm happy that Deus has shown herself,
but in my current state it would be
impossible for me to absorb her power.
So, Shido Itsuka,
in order to reach her,
I'll be claiming the Spirit power
you possess first.
What?!
Sandalphon!
Zadkiel!
Raphael!
Metatron!
Let's get started, Magus.
I'll finish this fast.
I won't even grant you time
to steel your resolve.
Yuzuru!
This space is already under
the dominion of Ein Sof Ohr.
Without any spirit power or magic power,
you'll only be wasting
your lives in this space.
Don't do it, Yuzuru!
Apologies.
I'm sorry.
Tohka...
Kaguya...
Yuzuru... Kaguya...
That's two down.
Why you!
You're a bit troublesome,
so I wanted to save you for last...
Are you all right, Tohka?
Mukuro?
Thanks, you saved me.
Are you okay, Tohka?!
Tohka, where are Kaguya and Yuzuru?
So that's the Spirit of Origin?
Hmph, she has a nasty air about her.
Ahh, it's been so long, Mana.
What'd you say?
I have to retrieve my Sephirah right now.
But there's no need for you to die, too.
You should back away.
Oh, well.
If I take this too slow, then Shin will return.
So I'll end this quickly.
That light's...
Elliot...
Hey. You awake?
I think we can say I won, yeah?
Kill me.
Huh?
Like you said, you've won, Elliot.
I can't afford to live in shame any longer.
What do you think you're doing, Elliot?!
What am I doing?
Rendering your enemy powerless
is a natural thing to do.
It's too dangerous
to let you keep that Realizer.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Why won't you kill me?!
The loser doesn't get to order
the winner around, dummy.
How dare you call me a dummy?!
You need to quit acting ridiculous!
I'm not being ridiculous.
It's my choice whether to kill you or not.
That's what I mean by being ridiculous!
Are you trying to make fun of me?!
That's why I called you a dummy.
Why are you always like this?
You've always made fun of me
and treated me like a child!
Even in this situation
you're showing me kindness!
Why won't you recognize me
as your enemy?! Why?!
Oh, shut up, shut up.
Be quiet for a bit.
Why didn't you take me with you, Elliot?
Hit my limit, huh?
Well, that came sooner than I thought.
I thought I would have time
to see Karen once more.
I'm sorry, Karen, Ellen.
Now, then.
Sorry, boy,
but it looks like this is it for me.
I leave the rest to you.
How pretty.
Ein Sof.
What on earth is this?
A territory?
But this is...
You're not mistaken.
DEM used this as a model
to develop their territory technology.
However, this territory of mine
is constantly deployed.
It lies just one thin membrane
outside of this world.
And I've currently summoned
a portion of its core, Ein Sof, here.
Which means the space surrounding me
is now the Neighboring World.
Neighboring World?
I don't know what kind
of power this Ein Sof holds.
However, that won't matter
as long as we stop you.
Michael, Segva!
Don't do it, Mukuro!
Mukuro!
Michael has the ability
to seal any and all things.
It's not impossible to seal
the power of Ein Sof with it.
I can't blame you for reaching that judgment,
but this is the Neighboring World
encroaching on this world.
It's my world.
All of its rules and natural laws
are different from this world.
Attacking Ein Sof in here
is set to "impossible".
Yes.
In this world, everything is as I will it.
That's three down.
We're running!
As expected, Mana.
Good judgment.
Now...
I'll make it so none in this world
are able to escape it.
You added more rules?!
Tsk, so anything goes then?!
That's right.
Everything in this world obeys my will.
Wha?!
Mana, I've caused you trouble for a long time.
Let go of me!
Mio?
Have you remembered for me?
Wait just a little bit,
I'm sure Shin will need you.
Mana!
Metatron!
Metatron.
Zadkiel!
Hmm, then I'll forbid that, as well.
Huh?
Yoshino!
Four down.
Episode 6
The Three Magi
Episode 7 "The World Tree Sheds Leaves"
Shido faces off against Westcott.
Meanwhile, the Spirits are driven
into a life-or-death crisis.
Next time is Episode 7:
"The World Tree Sheds Leaves."
Behold the ultimate finishing move.